[children shouting]
[shouting stops]
[girl] This is a true story.
It happened right here
in my town two years ago.
A lot of people die
in a lot of really weird ways
in this story.
but you're not gonna find it
in the news
or anywhere like that
because the police and
the top people in this town
were. like. so embarrassed
that they weren't able
to solve it
that they covered everything
all up.
But if you come here
and ask anyone.
they'll all tell you
the same thing
that I'm gonna tell you now.
This story starts
in my school.
Maybrook Elementary
is kindergarten
through fifth grade.
So this one Wednesday
is like a normal day
for the whole school.
And they had this teacher
who was new.
Her name was Justine Gandy.
And on this day.
she was going to her classroom
just like every morning.
But today was different.
Today. none of her kids
were there.
Every other class at that
school had all their kids.
Even the other third grade
Mrs. Belt taught was full.
But Mrs. Gandy's room
was totally empty.
Well. not totally.
There was one boy there.
And his name was Alex Lilly.
And he was the only kid
in the class of 18
that came to school that day.
And do you know why?
He was the only one there
because the night before
at 2:17 in the morning.
every other kid woke up.
got out of bed.
walked downstairs.
opened the front door.
walked across the front yard
and into the dark.
And they never came back.
["Beware of Darkness" playing]
♪ Watch out now ♪
♪ Take care
Beware of falling swingers ♪
♪ Dropping all around you ♪
♪ The pain
That often mingles ♪
♪ In your fingertips ♪
♪ Beware of darkness ♪
♪ Watch out now ♪
♪Take care
Beware of greedy leaders ♪
♪ They take you
Where you should not go ♪
♪ While weeping Atlas cedars ♪
♪ They just want to grow ♪
♪ Grow and grow ♪
♪ Beware of darkness ♪
♪ Beware of darkness... ♪
[girl] All the parents
and people at the school
were really sad and upset.
The police could tell
that the kids left at 2:17
because. like. half the houses
had alarms
that got tripped
when they walked outside.
Some of the kids
even got videoed
by the houses
that had cameras.
But the cameras
only showed the kids
walking out into the darkness.
They didn't show
where they went after that.
The police talked
to Alex a lot.
They asked him why his
classmates did what they did.
but he told them
he didn't know.
They asked him
if there was a plan.
but he said if there was.
he never heard it.
They asked him
if there was a TV show
where someone ran away
like that.
but he said if there was.
he never saw it.
They also talked to Mrs. Gandy
a whole bunch.
but she also
didn't know anything
and couldn't help them.
For almost a whole month.
they kept the school closed
for their big investigation.
But after a while. they had to
open everything back up.
so that the kids that didn't
disappear could learn again.
One night before they did.
they had a big meeting
at the school.
There was a bunch
of counselors
and people like that
to help everybody figure out
how to feel
and be sad together. I guess.
This is where the story
really starts.
[man] What's important is
that we don't judge our grief.
We might experience emotions
we don't like.
Emotions besides sadness.
We need to make sure
that we allow ourselves
to feel emotions like anger.
Anger is a very healthy part
of the grief cycle.
It can be especially powerful
in instances of abandonment.
Now. there are often times
that we...
[parent 1]
What does that mean?
"Especially powerful
in instances of abandonment"?
Are you saying that we should
be upset with Matthew?
I'm saying it wouldn't
be abnormal...
[parent 1]
I'll tell you right now
that you may call
what happened "abandonment."
but I don't.
I don't see it like that.
I see something that doesn't
make any sense at all.
We're talking about 17 kids
in one classroom.
What happened
in that classroom?
Why just her classroom?
Why only hers?
- [parent 2] Yeah!
- [others shout]
[counselor] Look. I'm
picking up a lot of emotion.
and that's fine.
[parent 1] So you'll
forgive me if I'm not
particularly interested in
hearing any more out of you.
I wanna hear
from Justine Gandy.
- [parent 2] Yeah.
- [others shout]
[parent 1] She's here.
I wanna know exactly
what she was doing in there.
[overlapping shouting]
[clears throat]
Uh...
I've...
First...
I just wanna say
how very sorry I am for...
all of what's happened.
I know there's nothing
I can say to make this better.
The truth is.
is that I want an answer
- just as bad as all of you.
- [parents shouting]
- [parent 3] Finally. Liar!
- [parent 4] That bitch.
I love those kids.
[parents muttering]
And...
[parents shouting out]
I... I know...
[parent 5]We know you know
exactly what's going on.
I know... I know it's...
it's not...
She should be locked up until
she tells us what happened!
[parents shouting]
Okay. now that kind of thing
is really not called for.
I'm serious.
Mrs. Gandy is here
as an affected member
of this community.
and she is hurting
just like all of us.
[parent 6] You're either
negligent or complicit!
[parents shouting]
[parent 7] Where are
our children. Mrs. Gandy?
That's enough. Everybody needs
to give us some space.
Please. Please.
It's been a long. long night.
We need to get some sleep.
wake up tomorrow
with clearer heads.
[shouting continuing]
Do you have anyone
you can stay with tonight?
- Mm-mmm.
- Then I recommend you going
straight home and laying low.
This feels like
it could turn in...
[person laughing nearby]
[people chatting]
Excuse me. ma'am.
I'm saving up for a bus ticket
to see my brother. Do you have
any change on you at all?
No. I'm sorry. Sorry.
[music playing
through PA system]
[phone buzzing]
Hello?
[heavy breathing on line]
[heavy breathing continues]
- Who is this?
- You better watch your back
because tonight's the
night that I...
Excuse me. miss.
I'm saving up for a bus ticket
to see my brother.
Do you have any change?
- No. sorry.
- Okay. thank you.
[people chatting. shouting]
[crickets chirping]
- [bottles clinking]
- [bag thuds]
[Justine exhales]
[people chatting]
[Justine sighs]
Anything the user does.
ZipString follows.
The string flies
at around 35 miles per hour.
and yet is safe to the touch.
All right. Sharks. watch this
trick. It's called the swirl.
This one's the corkscrew.
This one's the step-through.
[doorbell rings]
And pop!
Presenting the portal!
[Austin Hillam]
ZipString glides...
Hello?
Yes?
[dog barking]
- [dog barking]
- [Justine panting]
[sighs]
[pounding on door]
- Jesus! Fucking what?
- [pounding stops]
Who's there?
Hello?
Fuck!
[dog barking]
[children playing]
[principal] You're gonna keep
your health insurance.
and if you don't
mind me saying.
there's a lot of mental health
specialists on the plan.
Some of them are...
I. uh...
I just need to work. you know?
I just need to fill my days
with. uh...
Yeah. I... I need to work.
So... [chuckles]
Justine. the scene last night
was just proof
that we have a lot
of emotional parents here.
For now. I think it's best
if you keep some distance
from this place
until folks find time
to sort themselves out.
[child screeching]
How's Alex? Is he...
Alex is doing well.
He's in Mrs. Belt's class.
and we've been advised
that the best thing
that we can do for him
is keep him on a routine.
[inhales]
Keep his life as normal
as possible.
I would like to speak
with him.
We've had this
conversation before.
That's out of the question.
Well. I would...
I would feel so much better
if I could just
speak with him.
- Right there.
- What?
That's the problem.
You'd feel so much better.
He's been scrutinized
by the press.
He's had investigators
ransack his house.
He's been traumatized.
Let's try and put Alex
first. yes?
If you're implying
that I don't care
about Alex. or the students...
The issue isn't you caring
or not caring.
The issue here is.
you have a pattern
in which you overstep
professional lines
- with the students.
- Oh. my God. Here we go.
You know. I do not overstep.
You know it's not appropriate
to hug students.
Oh. I hugged a crying
little boy. Lock me up.
You know driving students home
is not professional.
What? She missed the bus.
She lived close to me.
- It's not appropriate.
- What...
[sighs] I know all of this
comes from the fact
that you care.
I know that you aren't
a threat to these kids.
but you have to realize.
you aren't a parent.
you're a teacher.
There's a difference.
And for that reason. no.
you cannot talk to Alex Lilly.
It's just...
We're the only ones left.
[people muttering]
- No way.
- Look. look. look.
[sniffles]
[whimpers]
Yeah. it's really
on there. huh?
Yeah. I've been
receiving phone calls as well.
- Threatening ones.
- Oh. yeah?
Think the caller might be
responsible for this?
I-I don't know.
Maybe. maybe not.
Yeah. well...
Whoever it was. the best
we can do is file a report.
Probably kids did this.
if you ask me.
I mean... [chuckles]
...hell. I used to do
stuff like this
when I was in school.
You know. TP houses.
ding-dong ditch.
I never wrote "witch"
on a car before.
but a buddy of mine
smeared some of his own...
["The Dark End of the Street"
playing]
Hey!
[both laugh]
Can we hug?
Yeah. of course we can hug.
Jesus.
What happened
to your hand there?
Oh. it was just a stupid
work accident thing.
- Nothing.
- Drink?
- Sure.
- Uh. Tony?
Tony?
Yeah. he'll...
he'll be here in a sec.
- That's fine.
- So...
- Yeah.
- I'm not in a rush.
- [chuckles]
- Um...
Wow. So I...
I didn't expect you to come.
I'm glad you texted. I...
You know. I've been thinking
about you a lot. and. uh...
I wanted to call.
but I didn't know if that
would make things worse or...
- I don't know what's...
- Yeah. well.
I'm not some
little delicate flower
that would wilt if I saw your
name pop up on my phone.
- I know that. I'm not saying--
- So. yeah.
Uh. Tony.
Uh. my friend wants a drink.
Hi. Hi.
- Uh. yeah. Go ahead.
- [Tony]How we doing?
Hi. Um. I'll get a Coke.
- A Coke?
- Yep.
Okay. fine. Whatever.
[chuckles]
So. what's going on?
How are you?
Well. everybody thinks
I'm a witch.
I don't think that's true.
Go look at my car.
Pfft.
I hope you didn't drive here.
Why do you hope
that I didn't...
I hope you didn't drive here
because...
Wait...
Don't be an asshole. Paul.
- I'm not being an asshole.
- Come on.
I'm not being an asshole.
I'm concerned
about you. and...
You know what? I don't need...
I don't need
your fucking concern.
Okay? I'm not drunk.
Okay. Got it. I'm sorry.
So what.
somebody vandalized your car?
They wrote "witch" across it.
So. yes.
For your information.
everybody thinks you're...
I'm a witch.
So. yes.
- One Coke.
- Thank you.
Can I give you a little. uh...
- Tough love?
- No.
Just some thoughts
from somebody
who knows you very well.
- Is that okay?
- Yep.
Try to get out
of your own head.
People are not all thinking
about you right now. okay?
The whole town
isn't aimed at you.
Hmm. I think you might
actually be wrong about that.
You have a tendency
to get a little "woe is me"...
- Wow. Wow. Okay.
- ...and a little paranoid.
And one thing I know
has never helped is this.
What is "this"? What?
A lonely drinking pity party.
I'm not lonely.
You're here.
You know what I mean. okay?
And I can't stay.
Does Donna know you're here?
No.
- Really?
- Really.
We're not... You know.
we're not happening right now.
Wow.
It's not a big deal.
Mm-hmm.
You're ridiculous.
Look at you. You're beaming.
Come on.
Have one real drink with me.
- Justine. no. Justine.
- Come on. Please.
Please?
No.
["Gotta Get Up" playing]
♪ Gotta get up
Gotta get out ♪
♪ Gotta get home
Before the mornin' comes ♪
♪ What if I'm late... ♪
Stop. please.
[song continuing]
You haven't changed a bit.
What do you got
going on today?
Work.
Working. All day. Till late.
Okay. I believe you. Jesus.
What?
Uh. don't-don't worry.
I'm not gonna be. like.
spam texting you
all day and night.
I learned my lesson.
Justine. I'm just saying
I'm working. That's it.
How's work?
It's fine. It's whatever.
Wow. I hope that's not
the general vibe over there.
What does that mean?
Well. there's 17
missing children out there.
and I like to think the people
in charge of finding them
aren't like. "Oh. whatever."
about their jobs.
First of all.
I'm not a detective.
I don't know if you know that.
Second of all.
I'm hungover as shit.
I didn't realize I was getting
grilled on the investigation.
[Justine] No. no. no.
I'm not...
I'm not trying to grill.
I'm just wondering if I need
to solve this thing myself.
[Paul] We're on it.
- You're on it?
- Yep.
Okay. well. what a load off.
You're on it.
Right now. you really
need to take it easy.
No one's slacking.
Don't let yourself get all...
Get all Justine about it?
Just leave the investigating
to the investigators.
It was great to see you.
You too.
[door handle clicking]
Suck my dick.
Subtitle | www.movieddl.me
[chiming]
[Justine patting her body]
Hello?
[crickets chirping]
[flies buzzing]
[gasps]
[clanging]
[principal]
I explicitly told you
not to interact with Alex.
Well. technically.
I didn't interact with him.
You followed him home.
You rang his doorbell
repeatedly
then spied through a window.
Well. can... can we
just focus on the fact
that that house is bizarre?
Justine. if I wasn't clear
with you before.
let me do so now.
I want you to leave him alone.
Okay. why were his windows
taped up?
Doesn't that seem strange
to you?
Probably because nosy people
take it upon themselves
to walk up
and peek through them.
- But. Marcus...
- Are you kidding?
I'm gonna do you the courtesy
of forgetting that this
phone call ever took place.
[door beeps]
[music playing
through PA system]
[Justine shrieks]
[grunts]
- What the fuck?
- You fucked him?
Donna?
- Donna. no. I...
I-I didn't fuck him.
- Yes. you did. I know you did.
- No. no. no. No. he...
He said you weren't together.
- Liar!
- No. no. no!
- You got him drunk!
- Donna. stop. Stop!
He was trying to be nice
to you. and you got him drunk!
- Hey! Hey! Don't!
- Stop!
[Donna] Look at what you did!
Look at what you did!
[woman on TV] Luciano. I know
we got off to a rocky start
with everything that happened
in the Jacuzzi.
but still you have made me...
[clock ticking]
[ticking continues]
[gasps]
[panting]
[clock ticking]
[muffled thudding]
[screaming]
[panting]
Oh. my God.
Alex. hi. How are you?
I-I just wanted to say hi
'cause I've been thinking
about you a lot. and...
I wanted to make sure
you're okay.
I'm okay.
Yeah?
'Cause I know it's been
a really hard time for me.
and I can't even imagine
how it's been like...
I have to go.
Hey. hang on. please.
I just...
I just want to make sure
- that everything's all right.
- Don't follow me!
Hello? It's Ms. Gandy.
I'd like to talk to you.
Hello?
I know you're home.
[crickets chirping]
[door opening]
[snipping]
[heavy breathing]
I'm going to work.
[keyboard clacks]
[clears throat]
[hammering]
Been calling you
all morning. boss.
Yeah. I hit a snag
on the way over.
[machinery whirring]
How things looking?
[chuckles] Little bit
of a chaotic morning.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Marc went to go pick up
the sodding.
but they didn't have it in
'cause the order
never got placed.
Shit. Goddamn it. That...
All right.
I'm sorry about that.
Yeah. we got the owner coming
Friday for a walk-through.
and we're still gonna
have the open frame in.
It's on me. It's my bad.
And then I showed up.
and I see that Alvin
painted the door with the
paint that you ordered. and...
Yeah?
They wanted forest green
and that's red.
- What?
- Look.
Goddamn it. Wait a minute.
Did they send the wrong...
I checked the order.
and we ordered it.
They sent what we asked for.
but what we asked for was...
All right. I fucked up.
I'll take it back.
get the right one.
[low chatter]
Mr. Graff.
Yeah.
We follow up on
every one of these calls.
So I can assure you
that as we speak.
we have officers
aggressively pursuing
every lead that comes
through this station.
So. what about the feds?
They got nothing new?
There continues to be a very
healthy information exchange.
So I can tell you
with full confidence
that they are also pursuing
every lead aggressively.
What's happening
with the K-9 units?
I haven't heard about any
K-9 reports in a long time.
That's because
they don't report to you.
Mr. Graff. I can understand
your passion.
And I don't mind having
these conversations with you
because. God forbid.
if it was my child.
I'd be demanding answers too.
But I need you to trust
that what we're doing here...
She's still not talking. huh?
She knows.
I disagree with that.
You're aggressively
following up on every lead.
and yet she's just out there
walking around free as a bird.
Have you done any looking
into her whatsoever?
Extensively. Yes. we have.
So you know about
her past. huh?
'Cause I've done some digging.
And I've found out a lot.
She had a DUI two years ago.
Did you not see that?
She was let go from her
last school that she taught at
for inappropriate behavior.
Did you not see
that one either?
With a member of the faculty.
She's a troubled person.
is she not?
What is it you think
that she knows?
What do you think it is
that she's not telling us?
Because those kids walked out
of those homes.
No one pulled them out.
No one forced them.
I don't see
anything whatsoever
that points to that woman.
What do you see that I don't?
I see something that
I don't understand at all.
[parent 1] Yeah!
We're talking about 17 kids
in one classroom.
And none of them
talked about it?
[parent 2] Exactly.
And we got how many parents
in here.
and none of us saw it coming?
[parents shouting]
I want to know what happened
in that classroom.
Why just her classroom?
Why only hers?
[overlapping voices]
[parent 3]
Where are our children?
[parent 4]
You're just gonna leave?
[Marcus] That's enough.
Everybody needs to give us
some space.
- Please. Please.
- [shouting continuing]
Let's all get
a good night's sleep.
Wake up with clearer heads.
Please.
- [parent 5] She has answers!
- [parents shouting]
[James] Excuse me. miss.
I'm saving up for a bus ticket
to see my brother. Do you have
any change on you at all?
[Justine] Sorry.
[gasps]
Matthew?
Matthew.
[hinge squeaks]
[panting]
Matthew!
Stop!
Wait.
[thunder rumbles]
[footsteps running up stairs]
Matthew?
[gasps]
Matthew. where are you?
Where did you go?
Talk to me.
Talk to me!
[sniffs. groans]
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that
I wasn't able to sa...
That I wasn't able...
I wanted to say it
so many times.
I really do want to say it
all the time
because I feel it
all the time.
I love you so much.
[shouts]
[grunting. panting]
What the fuck?
Where's our house?
There.
Where's the tower? Tower.
tower. tower. tower. tower.
Ah.
Show me.
Come on.
[bell chiming]
Hi.
- Hello.
- How are you?
I'm Archer Graff.
I'm Matthew's...
Yeah. I know who you are. Hi.
Oh. good. I know we haven't
spoken before directly.
We've seen each other
at a lot of the same...
- How are you. Archer?
- I'm good. I'm real good.
I... You know.
All things considered. just...
soldiering on.
We have to. don't we?
We do.
Listen. I'm sorry to
surprise you at home like this
in the...
in the middle of the day.
But. um. I don't know
if you know.
but we got some footage of
Matthew leaving the house
on our Ring cam thing here.
and I think you folks
had the same...
same situation with Bailey?
Yeah. that's right.
All right. Well. I'm sure
you showed yours to the police
just like I did. but I-I...
I wondered if you would mind
letting me take a look at it.
I don't need a copy
or anything.
I'm not comfortable with that.
Okay. I understand.
Gary?
Archer Graff. How you doing?
Fine.
Matthew's dad.
Yeah. [sighs] Of course.
How's it going?
Um. I have a strange question
I need to ask you.
It's kinda hard to watch this.
Okay. wait. Go back to where
she steps on the sidewalk.
Okay.
Uh...
Okay. Right there.
[Gary] What do you see?
One. two. three. four...
...five. six. seven.
Sorry.
Come on. What am I looking at?
Hey.
- I want to talk to you.
- Well. I...
I don't think we have anything
to say to each other.
I think you have a lot to say.
You and every other person
in this city.
Believe me.
the message is loud and clear.
I'm the problem. Got it.
You know what?
I think that's the first
honest thing
I've heard you say.
- You are the problem.
- You wanna get in my face?
- You wanna threaten me?
- I'm not...
Nobody's threatening you.
You're barking up
the wrong tree. Okay?
This whole victim persona
that you're taking on.
it might have
the police fooled.
the school fooled...
[speech fades]
- Stop thinking of yourself!
- Marcus?
You and I are gonna
have a conversation right...
- [Marcus grunting]
- [Justine straining]
[Justine gasping]
Hey!
[Marcus babbling incoherently]
- [Marcus snarling]
- [Justine shrieking]
Just stay down.
[panting. growling]
Hey!
[growling]
[snarling]
[shouts. growls]
[shrieking]
[Paul] Hotel's good. though?
- [Donna] It's fine.
- Yeah.
Not the Ritz. but I'm not
expecting them to go nuts.
Yeah. Well. it's only
for six nights. Right?
Three. actually.
Apparently.
I don't have to be here
for the big wrap-up shindig.
so I get to leave on Thursday.
- Isn't that great?
- Yeah. It's good.
'Cause I'm supposed
to ovulate Friday.
so we can hit the target
this month.
Nice. Okay. Yeah. Good.
I thought you'd like that.
Oh. will you tell my dad
when you see him today
that since I'll be back
for the weekend.
we can make their
anniversary lunch thing?
[sighs]
Yeah. I'll let him know.
He'll be happy.
You about to start your shift?
Yep.
You gonna hit
a meeting afterward?
Um. I wasn't planning on it.
Don't you think you should?
[sighs]
Uh. if I have time.
I'll hit one.
Paul. especially when
you're going to be
spending stretches alone.
I think it's important that
you go to regular meetings.
I'm not gonna drink. Donna.
I feel fine.
If I don't feel fine.
then I'll hit a meeting. Okay?
Okay. sweetie.
Okay. I gotta get going now.
Okay. Don't forget to tell
my dad about this weekend.
Yep.
- Love you.
Jesus Christ.
Hey. Ed.
Hey. buddy.
Uh. Donna's back Friday.
so we're good to have lunch
with you guys on Sunday.
Why's she coming back early?
I guess they're
cutting her loose. so...
she wanted me to let you know
that we're in.
Okay. Sounds good.
Anniversary lunch?
Yep.
That's nice.
Well. congratulations and...
- Well. thanks.
- A lot of years.
You calling me old?
No. No. sir. No. no. no.
Why would you call me old?
No. sir. I wasn't saying that.
I'm giving you shit.
Well. just starting
my shift here.
Roger that.
[man talking nearby]
["Don't Be Scared"
playing on radio]
[newsreader] Next Monday
will mark 30 days
since 17 grade-school children
have disappeared
from McCarren County.
Community members
have issued a $50.000 reward
for any information
leading to their recovery.
Any suspicious individual
or activity
should be reported to your...
[radio off]
- [single-tone siren]
- Stop right there. Police.
Shit.
[siren wailing]
[truck horn blares]
Stop or you're gonna
get the Taser!
[groaning]
Dude. please.
Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop.
- Shut up.
- Please. I work there. man.
I just lost my keys. Please.
I lost my keys. Please.
[man groaning]
- You okay?
- Yes. Officer. I'm okay.
All right. We went down
pretty hard there. You good?
Officer. I'm okay.
Just please call my warehouse.
You can look the number
up online.
My phone isn't working
right now.
Cuffs too tight? Hands okay?
Yes. they're okay. Officer.
- Let's walk back to the car.
- No. no. no.
Come on. Let's go.
One. two. three.
Please. Officer. Officer.
- Hey. what's your name. sir?
- James.
James. okay. Stand right here
for me. James.
- You got any weapons on you?
- No.
No? How about drugs?
Are you holding?
No. sir.
Anything in your pockets
gonna stick me
when I put my hands
in there. James?
No. sir. I do not.
Are you sure? I don't wanna
get poked by anything.
I have nothing. sir.
Okay. James.
Hold still for me there.
Shouldn't run
from the police. sir.
Ah! Fuck!
[panting]
Please. Please be okay.
Shit.
Okay. Up. Up. Get up.
- [James groans]
- Hey. Can you hear me?
James? You with me?
Ow. What the fuck?
Fucking hit me. bro.
Okay. Here's what's
gonna happen now.
I'm gonna take
these cuffs off you. okay?
I'm gonna get in my car
in a second.
I'm gonna drive away. but...
Are you listening to me?
I don't want to see you here
again. okay?
The way I see it.
I did you wrong.
you did me wrong.
Let's just call it a day.
But if I see you
out here again.
it's gonna be
a different story. Yes?
Yes?
I mean it.
Okay. consider yourself
warned. Now. let's get up.
I'm gonna take these cuffs
off you. One. two...
Because right now.
this is a...
this is a whole other matter.
Somebody needs to
just tell this guy
his kid is not
the only kid missing.
There's 17 kids. All...
[sighs]
Okay. listen.
As long as
this isn't reported.
that footage is gonna
sit on a drive somewhere.
and it's gonna get recorded
over in about a month.
And if that fucking citizen
doesn't come back here
in a month
and file a complaint.
this could all go away.
But if they do...
Paul. you're gonna be
in some serious hot water.
Did you get that hand
checked out?
Fuck!
[phone pings]
["The Dark End of the Street"
playing]
Hey!
Can we hug?
Yeah. of course we can hug.
Jesus.
[song continues]
[both grunting]
[sighs]
[Donna] Hello?
Paul?
Hey.
- Where have you been?
- You're home.
I am.
Someone got sick.
and they sent everyone
on my team. on Morris's...
Where have you been?
I was. uh... I was out.
Where?
Paul.
You piece of shit.
[officer 1]You wanna switch
up lunch today or same place?
- [officer 2] Yeah. pizza?
- Yeah. Lunch on you today?
[low chattering]
I have seen this issue...
Son of a bitch.
Hey!
What did I tell you? Huh?
What did I tell you?
What did I fuck...
Oh. you fucker.
[tires screech]
Fucker!
[James] This is fucking
bullshit. Look at this shit.
Please. please.
please. please.
Right here. right here.
right here. Yep.
[grunts]
Goddamn it. What the fuck!
Fuck.
Piece of shit. Yes.
Goddamn it.
Please. please. please.
Fuck! Fuck! Come on.
Goddamn it. Fucking go.
Yes. Goddamn it.
Argh! Fucking shit!
Fuck!
Yo. new phone.
[coughs] It's me. dude.
Um. dude.
I got a job yesterday.
Yeah. thank you. man.
Thank you. thank you.
thank you.
Yeah. um. so just. like.
a little teeny-tiny problem
'cause I just... I can't start
till I have. like. new shoes.
And. you know. a whole outfit.
'Cause. you know. like I said.
it's fancy.
And. um...
Wait. wait. wait.
No. no. no. Wait. wait.
This is a good thing.
I got... I got a job.
and I'm-I'm-I'm freaking...
I'm doing the thing.
So. you know.
we can start chilling again.
[groans] Of course
I'm gonna pay Mom back.
but I can't do that
until I get the. you know.
money to get the clothes.
so that I can do the job.
so that I can pay Mom back.
Hello?
Argh! You fucking bitch.
Fuck. Fuck. Fuck.
Hey. man. I feel like I wasn't
communicating very well
how important it is that I get
just. like.
a little bit of money.
so that I can get
the clothes for the job.
so that I can get the job.
obviously.
So please call me back so
I can communicate that better.
Thanks. buddy. Love you.
Hell. yeah!
No.
No?
I don't want.
What do you mean?
Why you no want? This is good.
These are good.
Look. this is worth.
like. 50 bucks.
No.
Twenty.
Ten.
Five.
Please. dude. Please.
Fuck.
[single-tone siren]
[Paul] Stop right there.
Police.
[siren wailing]
Fuck!
[groans]
[Paul] Way I see it. I did you
wrong. you did me wrong.
We're gonna call it a day.
But if I see you
out here again...
it's gonna be
a different story. Yeah?
Okay.
Consider yourself warned.
Get the fuck up.
[thunder rumbling]
Fuck!
The fuck off me. man.
What the fuck?
[straining]
[clattering]
Shit.
Oh. shit. No way. dude.
Oh. fuck. Willow.
Jesus! Fuck!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Um...
Hello?
You good?
[finger snaps]
[thud]
What the fuck?
[rattling]
[clattering]
[faint whispering]
[gurgling]
Sorry! Fuck! Sorry!
Sorry!
Fuck! [grunts]
What the fuck? What the fuck?
[grunting]
[panting]
Fuck.
Goddamn it. Piece of shit.
[cutlery clinking]
What the fuck? Jesus! Fuck!
Fuck! Goddamn it.
Fuck! Argh!
Please. please. please.
Fuck!
[pawnbroker]
20. 40. 60. 80. 100.
Hey.
I'm calling about
the $50.000 reward
for information
about the missing kids
'cause I know where they are.
I'm pretty sure all of 'em.
Looked like a bunch of 'em.
They're all standing
in the basement of this house.
just. like. standing there.
And. um...
I don't know.
They're in the basement
standing all still and shit.
And there's. like. fucking
two wackos over there.
And it's just. like.
fucked-up. [laughs]
Um. but-- So how's this...
how's this gonna work. though?
How do I get the money?
No. I'm not... I'm...
I'm completely serious.
I mean. I can show you.
Like. I'll show you.
Um. but I just... I. uh...
I really don't wanna come in.
'cause. like. someone...
Could someone come meet me
somewhere with the cash?
'Cause like... I just...
I really don't like
police stations. you know?
They just kind of freak
me out. I'm. uh... I'm phobic.
[Paul] Hey!
What did I tell you?
What did I fucking...
[James whoops]
"What'd I tell you. huh?
What'd I tell you?
- I'm a big cop. and I..."
- [giggle]
[gasps]
[crickets chirping]
[panting]
You're okay. You're okay.
That wasn't real. That wasn't
real. That wasn't real.
- It's okay. You're okay.
- [twig snaps]
[James panting]
[Paul screams]
[James] Fuck.
Fucker! You stabbed me!
No. no. no. I'm sorry.
Sorry. It was an accident.
It was an accident. I'm sorry.
Wait. wait. wait. Wait. wait.
Wait. wait.
I know where those kids are.
That's why I was coming
to the station.
- You're fucking lying!
- No. no. no. I'm not. I'm not.
I promise. I promise. I know
where they are. I promise.
Where?
[stammering]
They're at-at-at a house.
not far. in the basement.
What the fuck are you t...
What house?
I... I can show you. man.
It's-it's really. really.
really close.
Oh. fuck me.
Do you have AIDS?
Huh?
AIDS. asshole.
Do you have AIDS?
Uh...
Uh. I don't think so.
Hepatitis? Shit like that?
I mean. shit.
not that I know of.
That one. the dark one.
Right there
at the end of the block.
Um. excuse me. sir.
Um. I don't want to be rude.
but. like.
how do I know you aren't
gonna try and. like.
take that reward for yourself?
Sir?
Officer?
Oh. man.
[no audible dialogue]
[mouthing words]
What the fuck?
[crickets chirping]
What the fuck? [groans]
Let me the fuck out of here.
Goddamn it.
Oh. Thank you.
[whispering] What the fuck?
Jesus Christ. What the fuck?
Hey. yo. you good?
- [Paul snarling]
- Jesus Christ. bro!
- Hey! Get off me. bro!
- [Paul growls]
Get the fuck off me!
Hey! Fuck!
Help me! Help me!
Someone. please help me!
[Justine] I'm telling you.
Marcus. I've seen it myself.
There's something
very. very wrong
going on inside of that house.
If you don't believe me.
- go there yourself.
- Justine. stop.
Here's the bottom line.
Alex has been
traumatized enough
by the events
of the last two months.
- as I'm sure you have.
- Marcus...
Which is why I'm gonna do
you the courtesy
of forgetting that this
phone call ever took place.
If a child's welfare
is questioned. by law...
- Justine.
- ...you have to refer it
to CPS.
By law.
Are you really gonna
take it there?
Is this the corner
you're gonna put me in?
Just go make the house call.
Marcus. Just do that.
I'm not authorized
to just make house calls.
Well. you're a mandatory
reporter. You have to.
Okay. here's what I'll do.
I'll invite his parents to
come in. have a talk with me.
We'll have a face-to-face
at the school.
Is that acceptable to you?
Yes. thank you. I would
really appreciate that.
Okay. then. You're welcome.
Goodbye.
- [knocking at door]
- Yeah.
Your two o'clock is here.
That's fine.
Well. send them in. please.
Marge.
This way. ma'am.
Principal Miller. I'm Gladys.
Yes. H-Hi. Hi.
Come on in.
- Have a seat. please.
- Oh. thank you.
Thank you. Marge.
Thank you for coming in. I...
I know you guys have had
a lot of attention lately.
Not all of it
could possibly be wanted.
I'm happy to come by.
It's fine.
Okay. Forgive me...
We have not met.
Is that right?
No. I don't think so.
- Okay... Phew.
- [Gladys laughs]
Because I was relatively
certain I'd remember.
I know I've met
Alex's father before.
I'm Alex's aunt.
and his mom's my baby sister.
Okay. So you're not
his legal guardian.
Well. no. That would be
his parents. of course.
Okay. Well. uh...
Forgive me. Gladys.
but unfortunately. I need
to speak with his parents.
[sighs]
Well. I hate to say it.
but his parents have been
feeling unwell as of late.
and I'm staying with them
to help take care of Alex.
Oh. S-Sounds serious.
Oh. no. No. it's not serious.
Nothing terminal.
It's just a touch
of consumption.
"A touch of consumption"?
Yeah.
You know what?
I'm embarrassed to say
I guess I don't really know
what that means.
I thought it was something
settlers got
on the Oregon Trail.
[both laughing]
- What is it? Tuberculosis?
- You know what?
They are doing just fine.
but they need to stay home.
I had hoped to speak to them
in person because...
[inhales]...this is awkward.
but a concerned individual has
lodged a welfare complaint.
And unfortunately.
I need to make contact
with the child's
legal guardian.
It's something
that's not really negotiable.
I need to speak
with their parents in person.
Oh. dear.
I could come over to the house
if that would make it easier.
I'm just trying to avoid
involving CPS.
- But frankly...
- CPS?
...I'm not convinced
that anything is wrong.
Who made the complaint?
I'm not at liberty to say.
Well. this is very upsetting.
[TV] It is now that
all free will has been lost.
The ant moves
under the direction
of a mind separate
from its own.
Here. the ant initiates
its death grip.
Yum. yum. yum.
There we go.
As the parasitic Cordyceps
continue to feed of fits body.
That's disgusting.
Fungal fruiting occurs next.
- Large blooms...
- [doorbell rings]
...that serve
to spread more spores...
Who could that be?
...that will find more ants.
[man] Ew.
[panting]
- Thank God you're home.
- [man] Who is it?
I'm so sorry to disturb you
on a Saturday.
Oh. will you please.
please forgive me?
We're just sitting down.
The bus didn't pick me up
where it was scheduled to.
And I had realized
far too late...
[inhales]
...that I was standing
on the wrong corner.
And by the time
I put that together.
oh. I'd missed it entirely.
So I had to walk all the way
across town to get here.
Well. I'm so sorry
to hear that...
I am sorry to tell you this.
sweetie.
but I am on the verge
of collapse.
Oh.
Could I please
have some water?
I'm afraid that's re...
Of course
you can have some water.
Oh. thank you so much.
I'm afraid
it's really not a...
My name's Gladys.
it's so nice to meet you.
Hi.
Oh! I absolutely love
this house.
Look. a giraffe
and a green Chinese la...
That's original in there.
I bet it is.
[clapping]
Oh. I just love this kitchen.
Clean. white cabinets.
How I'm envious of that.
[laughs]
Now. listen.
I know that it's inconvenient.
but I really needed
to speak to you
about our conversation
yesterday.
[coughs] Oh.
[coughs]
Marcus. get her a glass.
A bowl. please.
A bowl?
Yes. a bowl.
It's a peculiarity of mine.
I don't even try
to rationalize it anymore.
A bowl of water. Okay.
Thank you.
I-I wanted you to know that
I talked to Alex's father.
who's very ill. as I said.
But the good news is.
he's more than happy
to come in Monday.
sit down with you
and clear everything up.
I appreciate that.
but it really is unnecessary.
So there's no need to contact
the authorities. right?
That's. uh...
Sure. I guess not.
I mean. you haven't
contacted them yet. right?
Gladys. I'm really gonna
have to insist that you. uh...
Is... Is that my ribbon?
You haven't
contacted them. right?
No. I haven't. What is this?
[man] Oh. my God!
Whoops! Look what I did.
Oh. my goodness.
Why did you do that?
Well. it was an accident.
of course.
Wow. That's really bleeding.
Terry. go get the alcohol
- and the first aid kit.
- Okay.
Oh. no. no. no.
That's nonsense.
Could you get me
a rag. sweetie?
[stammering]
[shrieks]
I think she cut my hair!
I'm calling 911.
Marcus. I think
she cut my hair!
Marcus. what did she do?
[dings]
[choking. panting]
Marcus?
[gasps]
[gurgling]
- Well...
- [thudding]
[groaning]
- [Gladys humming]
- [thudding continues]
[Marcus groaning and panting]
[sighs]
- [Marcus panting]
- [dog barking]
[person on street] Look!
[car tires screech.
horn honks]
[person in park]
Yo. what the fuck. man?
[people in park shouting]
[person at table] Oh. my God.
[panting continuing]
[Archer]Come out with it.
Just think of the kids.
- Stop thinking of yourself!
- [Justine] Marcus?
- You and I are gonna have a...
- [Marcus snarling]
- [Justine shrieking]
- [Marcus grunting]
[Archer yells]
[snarling]
[Archer] Stay down.
Hey! Stop! No!
Oh. my God. [whimpering]
Help me. please. Please.
Oh. God. No! [screams]
- [whimpering]
- [door chimes]
[shrieking]
Oh. my God.
[screaming]
[shrieking]
[Archer] Hey!
Oh. my...
[gasping]
[whimpers. babbles]
- Get out of my store!
- Fucking help me!
[shrieking]
- [Marcus growling]
- [screaming]
[Marcus babbling]
[snarling]
[Justine screaming]
What the fuck?
[groaning]
Motherfucker.
Come on. you piece of shit.
[muffled screaming]
[screaming continuing]
[woman screaming]
[sound becomes clearer]
[woman continues screaming]
[low chattering]
[no audible dialogue]
Are you okay?
Yeah. I think so.
I'm just. uh...
scraped up.
You?
The same.
I-I wanna thank you.
- Ah...
- No. I do. So. thank you.
Sure.
I mean. what else could I do?
Guy was out of control.
The last time I talked to him.
he was fine.
I mean. he really was.
[stammers]
I've never seen anything
like that in my life.
I have.
What are you talking about?
The way he was running.
I've seen that before.
Can I show you something?
Their little girl ran
the same way Matthew did.
Same posture. same exact way.
Just like Marcus
ran after you today.
He was weaponized.
Like a heat-seeking missile
just locked onto you.
So. here. Look at this.
This is my house.
This is Bailey Kramer's house.
Now. if you assume they were
heading in a straight line
at just some target of theirs.
and you assume they both had
the same target.
those lines intersect
somewhere around here.
Oh. my God.
There must be something
about this area.
- Alex.
- Some-- What?
Alex Lilly lives
in this house.
[teacher] Who else can think
of an example of a parasite?
Anyone?
- Lisa?
- A tapeworm.
A tapeworm! Very good!
That's a gross one. right?
It lives in your intestines
and it eats your food.
[children chattering]
Stop it.
"Stop it."
- "Stop it."
- [other children laughing]
"Stop it."
[children chatter. shout]
[man] What's up. Axe Man?
Talk to me. Axe Man.
How was school today?
- Good.
- Good? Kiss any supermodels?
[chuckles] No.
No? All right.
Well.
tonight's the night. pal.
Your mom's aunt Gladys
is coming. remember?
[sighs] Why do we have to
have her live at our house?
'Cause it's like
we talked about.
She's sick. and she doesn't
have anywhere else to go.
But I don't even
know her. though.
Pfft. I hear you. bud.
I don't know her either.
To be honest. I'm not sure
your mom knows her that well.
But she's family.
Family's important.
We gotta help each other out.
Hey. found a kid.
Hey. My men have returned.
- Hi.
Whoa. Hey. Good day at school?
- Yeah.
- Okay. good.
Uh. I would really like to
get this house cleaned up
before your aunt Gladys
gets here.
So do me a favor.
get your room cleaned up
before you start
your homework.
She's not coming in my room.
is she?
I'd really like a clean house.
That includes your room.
so let's go.
I know. It's horrible
cleaning up after yourself.
[car doors shutting]
[dad] All right?
[mom] Hi! Come in!
- [dad] Got the door?
- [mom] I got it.
[dad] One more step.
[dad] I'm just saying
she looked really bad.
I don't know if this
is the place for...
Yeah. well. it's either here
or out on the street. Stephen.
Well. you know. this ain't
a hospice place. hon.
I know that. I know.
We're not equipped for this
kind of thing. All right?
We hadn't seen this woman
in 15 years.
She didn't even show up
to our wedding...
Look. my mom
would do this for her.
so I'm gonna do this
for her. okay?
I could really
use your support.
If at any point
you feel like...
Alex. honey.
what are you doing?
I'm hungry.
Oh. you're hungry.
Okay. All right.
Well. go downstairs. eat up
and then go brush your teeth.
okay? It's almost 7:30.
And be quiet back there.
Your aunt Gladys is sleeping.
[door creaks]
[door creaking]
[gasps]
How long
is she gonna stay with us?
Hard to say. pal.
Doesn't look like
she's getting much better.
So she's gonna stay
with us forever?
No.
I...
I don't think she'll be here
longer than a month.
[children chattering]
- All righty. man.
- All righty.
I'll pick you up
at 2:00. okay?
- See ya.
- I love you.
- Love ya.
[Justine] That's time.
Pencils down.
Matthew!
What?
You said. "Pencils down."
Matthew. outside now.
Alex. are you okay?
I'm fine.
Matthew. let's go.
Get your bag.
It was a joke. Oh. my God!
- [bell ringing]
- [students chattering]
- You miss your ride. son?
- I'm okay.
You sure?
Mom. Dad. where were you?
Hey. Axe Man. How was school?
What's wrong?
Alex?
Oh. welcome home.
[chuckles]
How are you. sweetie?
Let me take a look at you.
Oh. you know.
I haven't seen you
since you were
a little teeny baby.
What's wrong with my parents?
Oh. nothing. sweetheart.
They're just fine.
Mom.
Hey. How was school?
You see? I told you.
she's just fine. Don't worry.
Alex.
Now. don't be rude.
Why don't you sit down
at the table?
'Cause I'm making dinner.
I should have asked you.
but you weren't here.
so I thought mac and cheese
would...
Dad!
Alex. that's it.
I want you to go upstairs.
wash your face.
brush your teeth.
and then it is bedtime.
No dinner for you.
I'm not kidding. young man.
Go.
Come. Sit.
Alex.
Sit.
Don't worry about
your parents.
They're just resting.
Now. before you go to school
today. I want you to promise
that you will not tell
a living soul that I am here
or that your parents
are resting like they are.
Do you hear me. Alex?
Watch.
Ooh.
Are you watching?
Stop!
Stop. Dad!
Alex.
Sit down.
Now. when I tell you
that you are not to speak
about me or your parents
to anyone...
you understand what can happen
if you break your promise.
I can make your parents
hurt themselves.
I can make them
hurt each other.
I can make them eat each other
if I want to.
Do I want to. Alex?
Do you believe me?
Promise you will not
talk about me
to another human being.
Say it.
I promise.
'Cause I'll know. Alex.
Go to school. Take the bus.
No talking today.
Good boy.
You'll need to
feed your parents.
There's soup in the cabinet.
Tomorrow.
you'll get some more.
[students shouting.
chattering]
[Gladys. distant] Alex.
Alex?
[Gladys coughs]
Come here. sweetie.
[labored breathing]
Oh.
I'm very sick. Alex.
Would you like some water?
Well. water won't help me.
I'm too sick for water.
I have been
for a very long time.
What will make you better?
Well. I was hoping
your mom and dad
would make me feel better.
but it doesn't seem to be
turning out so good.
Would you like to go
to a hospital?
Hospital won't fix me.
But maybe you could. though.
You could help.
How?
Well. at school.
bring an object from each
of your classmates home to me.
That might work.
How will that make you better?
It might be just what I need.
And if you got better.
you'd go back home?
If I got better...
I'd go back home.
[laughs]
Alex.
What are you doing in here?
Um. I didn't
feel like playing.
and I forgot something.
Whoa. whoa. whoa.
Hey. hey. hey.
Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
You've been
awful quiet lately.
Quieter than usual.
How are you doing?
I'm okay.
I just forgot something.
It's okay.
Alex. you know.
if... you ever want to talk
to someone.
you can always talk to me.
Do you know that?
Yeah.
You can talk to me
about anything you want.
I wanna go back now.
Okay. Go play.
[clanking]
[scraping. muffled speech]
[noise continuing]
What are you doing?
[rings]
[Justine laughing]
No...
[Gladys] Stephen here suffered
a stroke a little while back.
so he's unable to speak.
And I'm taking care of
the family for the time being.
I'm glad you both are here.
Alex. how are you doing. pal?
I'm okay.
[detective 1]Now. we're gonna
ask you some questions
about what happened
at school. okay?
Tomorrow.
people will come here.
And they will search
this house...
and we have to be ready.
[doorbell rings]
Detective. come in!
Good morning. Ms. Lilly.
- How are you today?
- Fine.
- Good to see you again.
- Nice to see you too.
- Remember Detective Colbert?
- Oh. yes.
We just wanted to come by the
house for a few minutes today
and look around. uh.
see the environment
that Alex has been living in.
And just get an idea of what
the family dynamic is like.
- Okay!
- Oh. Thank you.
And... Oh.
Hey. Alex.
How are you doing today?
He's a little quiet today.
right?
- Mm-hmm. Yes. he is.
- Okay.
Hello?
Pack your things. Alex.
we're leaving tomorrow.
Don't step over the salt.
[car approaching]
The cops are here.
What do you think that means?
I don't know.
Do we knock? Do we come back?
Maybe we knock.
And say what? What...
What are we gonna explain?
Yeah. I don't know.
- Let's just...
- Here we go.
Hey. what is this?
Is that the cop?
That's Paul.
- You know him?
- Yeah.
[creaking]
Hello?
Paul?
[voice trembling] Paul.
what are you doing back there?
[Archer] Wait.
[James screeching]
- [Paul screeching]
- [Justine screams]
[muffled shouting]
- [Justine screaming]
- [Archer shouting]
- [thudding]
- [Justine screaming]
[sounds of struggle
continuing]
[James snarling]
[Archer yells]
[Justine screaming]
[yells]
[shrieking]
Fuck! Fuck! [grunts]
- [snarling]
- [Justine screams]
Stay fucking back!
- [bell dings]
- [mom and dad screeching]
Paul.
Paul. stop.
Stop!
[Justine straining]
[Paul growling]
[panting. growling]
- [James snarling]
- [Archer grunts]
God.
Goddamn it.
[James yells]
[panting]
[crashing. glass breaking]
You goddamn freaky little...
[James yells]
[screeching]
Paul. Please.
Please.
[gurgling]
[panting]
- [banging]
- [growling]
[mom and dad screeching]
- [James snarling]
- [Archer grunting]
[Justine panting]
- [pounding on door]
- [mom snarling]
Matthew?
Matthew!
No.
Matthew.
[mom screeching]
[Dad growling]
[pounding. screeching
continue]
Matthew?
Come on.
Who...
- [pounding]
- [mom and dad shouting]
[sobbing]
[footsteps running up stairs]
[Justine gasps]
[screaming]
[Gladys] That's good.
Just like that.
[mom and dad screeching]
That's the way.
Oh. no.
[running footsteps]
[children screeching]
[shrieking]
[Gladys whimpering]
[children screaming]
[wailing]
Oh. God!
[Gladys wailing]
[lawn mower engine stops]
[screeching]
- [child snarling]
- [Gladys whimpering]
[children screeching]
[Gladys screaming]
Get off of me! Get off of me!
[gasping]
[screeching]
- [screaming]
- [children screeching]
[bell dings]
- [Justine gasps]
- [Archer panting]
Matthew?
[panting]
[whimpering]
[homeowner]
Honey. look outside.
Look what they did
to the yard.
Jeremy.
there's glass everywhere.
Find her shoe! My god!
Oh. my God. Oh. my God.
Now there's a man
in the kitchen!
[Justine panting]
Alex?
Matthew?
Oh. I found you.
[child narrator]
Alexys parents are still
being fed soup somewhere.
But not by him.
He moved to another town and
lives with a different aunt.
I heard that one
is a nice lady.
All of the kids from his class
got reunited
with their parents.
Some of them even started
talking again this year.
["Under the Porch" playing]
[song fades out]